Paul Abelson Papers 5192
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Cloaks and Suits Agreements, 1910-1933 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Protocol Cases, 1911-1913 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  Includes minutes, reports, correspondence
- Security Trust Fund, Correspondence, 1919-1922 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Grievance Board, correspondence, statistics RE: grievances, 1911-1913 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Grievance Board, correspondence, statistics RE: grievances, 1911-1913 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Articles, 1911-1914 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  Typed copies of articles and correspondence, translation of articles
- Articles, 1911-1914 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Special meeting of the Board of Arbitrators Selected by the Representatives of the Cloak and Skirt Makers' Unions of New York and the Cloak and Suit and Skirt Manufacturers Protective Association, 1913 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  Oct. 3rd-13th, 392 pg
- Meeting of the Board of Arbitrators In the Cloak and Suit Industry, 1914 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  January 14th-24th, 66 pg
- Adjourned Session of the Board of Arbitrators In the Cloak and Suit Industry, 1914 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  January 23rd-24th
- Arbitration Proceedings, The Cloak and Skirt Makers' Unions of N.Y. and Cloak, Suit and Skirt Manufacturers Protective Association, 1913 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  Aug. 3rd- 6th
- Meeting of the Joint Board of the Cloak and Skirt Makers' Union of I.I. and the Cloak, Suit and Skirt Manufacturers Protective Association, 1913 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  July 8th, 781 pg
- U.S. Commission on Industrial Relations, "Discussion on Question of Differences Between the Manufacturers' and Workers in the Cloak, Suit and Waist Industry"., 1914 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  January 15th-17th, 536 pg, New York City
- Cloak, Suit and Skirt Manufacturers Protective Association, "The Cloak Makers Strike"., 1910 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  158 pg
- Monarch Doll Co. vs. Doll and Toy Workers Union (DTWU), #18230, 5/34, 1934 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Ideal Novelty and Toy Co. vs. DTWU, #18230, 7/16/35, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  July 16th
- Monarch Doll Co. vs. DTWU, #18230, 7/16/35 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Doll Manufacturers Assn. of NY vs. DTWU, #18230, 9/14/35, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  September 14th
- Paragon Rubber Co. vs. DTWU, #18230, 9/14/35, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Knickerbocker Toy Co. vs. DTWU, #18230 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Expert Toy Co. vs. DTWU, #18230, 12/3/35, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  December 3rd
- Knickerbocker Toy Co. vs. DTWU, #18230, 3/11/36, 1936 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  March 11th
- Artistic Doll Co. vs. DTWU, #18230, 3/27/37, 1937 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  March 27th
- Admira Rubber Co. vs. DTWU, #l8230, 9/24/37, 1937 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Ideal Toy & Novelty Co. vs. DTWU #18230, 4/12/37, 1937 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Gund Manufacturing Co. vs. DTWU, #18230, 1/11/37, 1937 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  January 11th
- Alexander Doll Co. vs. DTWU, #18230, 6/15/37, 1937 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Gund Manufacturing Co. vs. Playthings and Novelty Workers of America (PNWA), Local 223, 7/11/38, 1938 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Admire Doll Co. vs. (PNWA) Local 223, 6/21/39, 1939 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Horsman Dolls, Inc. vs. DTWU, Local 225, 6/29/40, 1940 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Junel Novelties Inc. vs. United Paper, Noveltyand Toy Workers International Union, Local 223, 12/8/41, 1941 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Symphony Toy Co. vs. Playthings and Novelty Workers Local 223 6/8/42, 1942 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Symphony Toy Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 3/29/43, 1943 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Gay Stuffed Toy Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 9/10/43, 1943 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Character Novelty Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 11/16/43, 1943 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- World Toy Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 9/15/44, 1944 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Consolidated Toy Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 1/5/44, 1944 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Goldberger Doll vs. PNWA, Local 223, 5/9/44, 1944 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- ABC Toy Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 9/15/44, 1944 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- New York Doll Products Co. vs. PNWA, 9/15/44, 1944 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Ideal Rubber Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 10/26/44, 1944 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Victor Eckhardt vs. PNWA, Local 223, 11/l4/44, 1944 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Happy Doll vs. PNWA, Local 223, 11/l4/44, 1944 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Symphony Toy Co. vs. PNWA, Local 22, 12/4/44, 1944 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- J. Cey Toy Manufacturing Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223 12/18/44, 1944 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Jolly Toy Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 5/9/44, 1944 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Jolly Toy Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 10/26/45, 1945 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Uneeda Doll Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 11/30/45, 1945 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Ideal Novelty Co. vs. PNWA Local 223, 10/26/45, 1945 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Fiberoid Doll Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 10/26/45, 1945 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Block Doll Products Corporation vs. PNWA, Local 223, 1/25/45, 1945 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Mercer Doll Corp. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 3/27/45, 1945 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Expert Doll & Toy Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 3/27/45, 1945 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Miner Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 3/27/45, 1945 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Goldberger Doll Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 3/27/45, 1945 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Associated Doll Manufacturers of NY vs. PNWA, Local 223, 12/7/45, 1945 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Ideal Novelty & Toy Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- S&T Dolls vs. PNWA Local 223, 10/9/46, 1946 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- M&S Doll Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223 10/9/46, 1946 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Associated Doll Manufacturers of NY vs. PNWA, Local 223, 10/18/46, 1946 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- F&B Doll Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 10/21/46, 1946 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Uneeda Doll Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, ll/7/46, 1946 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Imperial Crown Doll Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 12/16A6, 1946 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- United Doll Parts Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 11/25/46, 1946 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Alexander Doll Co. vs PNWA, Local 223, 12/5/46, 1946 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Alca Novelty Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 12/5/46, 1946 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Natural Dolls Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 12/5/46, 1946 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Weiss Pulp Novelty Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223 12/5/46, 1946 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Doll vs. PNWA, Local 223, 12/11/46, 1946 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Gloria Toy Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223 9/20/46, 1946 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Art Doll Accessories vs. PNWA, Local 223, 4/19/46 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Imperial Crown Toy Co. vs. pnwa, Local 223, 11/25/46, 1946 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Exposition Doll & Toy Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 6/14/46, 1946 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Jolly Toys vs. PNWA, Local 223, 6/7/46, 1946 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- M. Flugelman vs. PNWA, Local 223, 1/14/46, 1946 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Novelty Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 1/14/46, 1946 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Gloria Toy Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 1/14/46, 1946 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Art Infants Wear vs. PNWA, Local 223, 3/22/46, 1946 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Merit Toy Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 3/22/46, 1946 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Art Novelty Infants Wear vs PNWA, Local 223 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Fairway Novelties vs. PNWA, Local 223, 6/10/46, 1946 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- P&M Doll Co. vs PNWA, Local 223, 8/14/46, 1946 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- S&T Novelty Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 6/20/46, 1946 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Sterling Doll Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 6/20/46, 1946 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Allied Doll Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 6/20/40, 1940 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Exposition Doll & Toy vs. PNWA, Local 8/14/46, 1946 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Jay-Zee Doll Hand Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 8/14/46, 1946 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Natural Doll vs. PNWA, Local 223, 8/14/46, 1946 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Novelties Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 3/22/46, 1946 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Sterling Doll Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 6/10/46, 1946 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Composition Novelty Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 4/29/47, 1947 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Happy Doll vs. PNWA, Local 223 12/4/47, 1947 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Vanity Doll Co, vs. pnwa, Local 223, ll/6/47, 1947 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Liberty Toy Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 10/8/47, 1947 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Weiss Pulp Products vs. PNWA, Local 223, 10/3A7 P&M Doll Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 10/3/47, 1947 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- S&T Novelty Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 9/10/47, 1947 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Uneeda Doll Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 9/10/47, 1947 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Ideal Novelty & Toy Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 1/14/47, 1947 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Natural Doll Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223 6/27/47, 7/16/47, 1947 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Rialto Toy & Novelty vs. PNWA, Local 223, 12/30/47, 1947 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Ideal Novelty & Toy Co, vs. PNWA, Local 223, 4/29/47, 1947 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- S&B Doll Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 4/29/47, 1947 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Doll Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 4/29/47, 1947 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Frish & Stern vs. PNWA, Local 223, 4/22/47, 1947 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Gerstenzang-Werner vs. PNWA, Local 223, 2/17/47, 4/22/47, 1947 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Buckingham Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 2/15/47, 1947 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Composition Novelty Inc. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 2/5/47, 1947 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Associated Doll Manufacturers of NY vs. PNWA, Local 223 1/14/47, 1947 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Associated Doll Manufacturers vs. PNWA, Local 22* 7/26/47, 9/10/47, 1947 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- National Association of Doll Manufacturers vs. PNWA, Local 223, 12/19/47 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- P&M Doll Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 9/22/48, 1948 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Belle Toy Co. vs. PNWA, Local 233, 12/20/48, 1948 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Ideal Toy & Novelty vs. PNWA, Local 233, 11/23/48, 1948 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Imperial Crown Toy vs. PNWA, Local 223, 11/18/48, 1948 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Effanbee Doll Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 11/10A8, 1948 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Fabroid Co. vs. PNWA, Local 233, 10/27/48, 1948 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Arranbee Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 10/22/48, 1948 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Gerstenzand & Werner Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 10/22/48, 1948 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Arranbee Doll Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 2/5/48, 1948 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Meyer Jocoby vs. PNWA, Local 223, 9/22/48, 1948 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Artistic Doll Co. vs. PNWA, Local 233, 6/3/48, 1948 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Duraltone Toy Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 6/3/48, 1948 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Ideal Rubber Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 3/16/48, 1948 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Frish Supply Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 3/4/48, 1948 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Happy Doll Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 3/4/48, 1948 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Eastern Rubber Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 3/4/48, 1948 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Zola Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 3/16/48, 1948 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- P&M Co. vs. PNWA, Local 233, 10/22/48, 1948 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- R&B Doll Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 6/3/48, 1948 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Meyer Jocoby vs. PNWA, Local 223, 6/7/49, 1949 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- National Assn. of Doll Manufacturers vs. PNWA, Local 223, 2/9/49, 1949 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Imperial Crown Toy Corp. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 4/7/49, 1949 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Picture Book Toys vs. PNWA, Local 223, 4/21/49, 1949 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Composition Novelty Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 4/21/49, 1949 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Cornet Doll Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 5/3/49, 1949 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Gerstenzand & Werner Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- F&B Doll Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 5/24/49, 1949 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Ideal Novelty & Toy Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 5/2A9, 1949 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Nu-Life Doll Co. vs. PNWA, Local 233, 6/15/49, 1949 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Jolly Toys vs. PNWA, Local 223, 6/15A9, 1949 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Frisch Doll Co. vs. PNWA, Local 233, 9/16/49, 1949 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Fabroid Doll Co. vs. PNWA, Local 233, 9/16/49, 1949 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Gund Manufacturing Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 10/4/1949 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Ideal -Rubber Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 10/4/49, 1949 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Art Infant's Wear vs. PNWA, Local 233, 12/19/49 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Gloria Toys vs. PNWA, Local 223, 5/5, 24/49, 1949 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Arranbee Doll Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 5/5/49, 1949 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Richard Kruger vs. PNWA, Local 233, 11/6/50, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- American Anode Inc. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 12/6/50, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Eugene Doll Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 12/6/50, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- F&B Doll Co. vs. PNWA, Local 233, 11/21/50, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Golderberger Doll Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- A&L Novelty Co. vs. PNWA, Local 233, 8/30/50, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Eastern Rubber Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 8/30/50, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Ideal Rubber Co. vs. PNWA, Local 233, 1/11/50 1/27/50, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Consolidated Toy Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223,6/27/50, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Alexander Doll Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 6/27/50, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Stephanie Playthings vs. PNWA, Local 223, 6/5/50, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Artistic Doll Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 4/25/50, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Novelty Doll Co. vs. PNWA, Local 233 1/27/50, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Fibroid Doll Co. vs. PNWA, Local 233, 7/14/50, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- P&M Doll Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 12/6/50, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- R.G. Kruger vs. PNWA, Local 223, 5/14/51, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- American Character Doll vs. PNWA, Local 223, 6/6/1951 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Belle Doll Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 6/6/51, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Goldberger Dolls vs. PNWA, Local 233, 6/26/51, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Eastern Doll Corp. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 8/31/51, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Ideal Novelty Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 9/20/51, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- General Doll vs. PNWA, Local 223, 10/5/51, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Natural Doll Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 11/8/51 M. Jacoby Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 12/6/51, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Happy Doll Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 5/14/51, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Roth Co. vs. PNWA, Local 233, 8/31/51, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Model Plastic Corp. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 10/8/51, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Happy Doll Co. vs. PNWA, Local 233, 2/1/51, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Saco Dolls vs. PNWA, Local 233, 9/20/51, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Sayco Doll Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 2/1/51, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Knickerbocker Toy Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 4/27/51, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Gay Stuffed Toy Co. vs. PNWA, Local 233, 2/1/51, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Ideal Novelty & Toy Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Monarch Doll Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 2/23/51, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Delux Toy Co. vs. PNWA, Local 233 2/23/51, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Artistic Doll Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 4/13/51, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Happy Doll Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 4/18/51, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- S.B. Novelty Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 4/20/51, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Belle Doll. Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 4/27/51, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Gund Mftg. Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 12/11/52, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- American Character Doll vs. PNWA, Local 223, 6/19/52 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Gund Mfg. Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 10/24/52, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Merit Doll Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 10/24/52, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Gloria Doll Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 10/24/52, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Art Infant Wear vs. PNWA, Local 223, 10/9/52, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Gund Mftg. Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 9/25/52, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Knickerbocker Toy Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 8/12/52, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Goldberger Doll Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 10/29/52, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Imperial Crown Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 1/16/52, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- American Character Doll vs. PNWA, Local 223, 5/21/52, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Uneeda Doll Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 5/16/52, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Royal Wig Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 4/28/52, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Matex Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 3/12/52, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Composition Novelty & Unique vs. PNWA, Local 223, 3/27/52, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Ideal Novelty Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 3/11/52, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Sayco Doll Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 9/16/52, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Imperial Crown Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 6/12/52, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Knickerbocker Toy Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 4/6/53, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Art Infant Wear Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 4/27/53, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Sibling Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 6/5/53, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- M&S Doll Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 4/l/53, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Expert Doll & Novelty Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 8/20/53, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Delux Toy Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 1/21/53, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Goldberger Doll Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 8/5/53, 8/19/53 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Art Infant Wear Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 3/12/53, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Gerstenzang-Werner vs. PNWA, Local 223, 2/6/53, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Model Plastic Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 2/6/53, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Kruger Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 2/4/53, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Elka Toy Co. vs. PNWA, Local 223, 10/22/53, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Gay Stuffed Toy vs. PNWA, Local 223, 10/5/53, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- F&B Doll Co. vs. PNWA Local 223, 2/5/53, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Eugene Doll vs. PNWA, Local 223, 10/5/53, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Grand Wig Co. v. PNWA, Local 223 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- R.G. Krueger v. PNWA, Local 223 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Assn. Doll Mnfgrs. v. PNWA, Local 223 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Best Toy Co. v. PNWA, Local 223 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Happy Doll Co. v. PNWA, Local 223 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Undated Decisions (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Correspondence, 1915-1944 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Correspondence, 1915-1944 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Correspondence, 1915-1944 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Correspondence, 1915-1944 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, 1915-1944 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Correspondence, 1915-1944 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Correspondence, 1915-1944 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Correspondence, 1915-1944 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Correspondence, 1915-1944 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Correspondence, 1915-1944 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Correspondence, 1915-1944 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Correspondence, 1915-1944 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Correspondence, 1945-1949 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Correspondence, 1945-1949 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Correspondence, 1945-1949 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Correspondence, 1945-1949 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, 1945-1949 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Correspondence, 1945-1949 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Correspondence, 1945-1949 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Correspondence, 1945-1949 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Correspondence, 1945-1949 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Correspondence, 1945-1949 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Correspondence, 1945-1949 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Correspondence, 1950-1953 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Correspondence, 1950-1953 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Correspondence, 1950-1953 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Correspondence, 1950-1953 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, 1950-1953 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Correspondence, 1950-1953 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Correspondence, 1950-1953 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Correspondence, 1950-1953 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Correspondence, 1934-1951 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Correspondence, 1934-1951 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Correspondence, 1934-1951 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Correspondence, 1934-1951 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, 1934-1951 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Correspondence, 1934-1951 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Correspondence, 1934-1951 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Correspondence, 1934-1951 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Correspondence, 1934-1951 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Clippings, articles, photographs, publications, miscellaneous minutes (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Clippings, articles, photographs, publications, miscellaneous minutes (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Juvenile Underwear Corp. vs. ILGWU, Local 10, 1939 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- L. Hochman vs. ILGWU, Local 10, 1939 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- David Korn & Co. vs. ILGWU, Local 10, 1939 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- May Knitting Co. vs. United Retail and Wholesale Employees of America, 1939 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- National Association of Blouse Manufacturers, Inc. vs. Blouse and Waist Makers Union, ILGWU, Local 25, 1938 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Musof & Bichwit vs. ILGWU, Local 6, 1916 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- R&K Regulation Dress Co. vs. Dressmakers Union, Local 91, 1932 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Associated Corset & Brassiere Manufacturers of NY vs. ILGWU, Local 32, 1939 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Correspondence, 1913-1925 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Correspondence, 1934-1939 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Correspondence (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Dress Agreements, 1913-1938 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Agreements, 1913-1938 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Arbitration Proceedings Between the Dress and Waist Manufacturers Association of NY and Ladies Waist and Dressmakers Union, Local 25, 1914 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Arbitration Proceedings Between the Dress and Waist Manufacturers Association and ILGWU, 1913 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Conference Between Local 25, ILGWU and the Dress and Waist Manufacturers Association, 1915 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Miscellaneous (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Minutes of Conference Committee of the Fur Industry, 1912-1924 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Minutes of Conference Committee of the Fur Industry, 1912-1924 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Minutes of Conference Committee of the Fur Industry, 1912-1924 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Minutes of Conference Committee of the Fur Industry, 1912-1924 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Minutes of Conference Committee of the Fur Industry, 1912-1924 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Minutes of Conference Committee of the Fur Industry, 1912-1924 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Minutes of Conference Committee of the Fur Industry, 1925-1932 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Minutes of Conference Committee of the Fur Industry, 1925-1932 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Minutes of Conference Committee of the Fur Industry, 1925-1932 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Minutes of Conference Committee of the Fur Industry, 1925-1932 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Minutes of Conference Committee of the Fur Industry, 1925-1932 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Minutes of Conference Committee of the Fur Industry, 1925-1932 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Minutes of Conference Committee of the Fur Industry, 1925-1932 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Minutes of Conference Committee of the Fur Industry, 1925-1932 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- First 300 cases, 1914-1916 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  Sept to Jan
- "Leading cases", 1914-1930 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  Sept to Dec
- Miscellaneous correspondence, lists of cases, etc., 1912-1932 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Cases, 1-70 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Cases, 71-160. (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Cases, 161-230 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Cases, 231-315 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Cases, 1929-1930 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Cases, 1930-1931 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Reports, 1914-1919 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Joint Board of Arbitration and Concilliation, 1914-1941 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Joint Board of Arbitration and Concilliation, 1914-1941 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Joint Board of Arbitration and Concilliation, 1914-1941 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Joint Board of Arbitration and Concilliation, 1914-1941 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Joint Board of Arbitration and Concilliation, 1914-1941 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Joint Board of Arbitration and Concilliation, 1914-1941 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Joint Board of Arbitration and Concilliation, 1914-1941 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Joint Board of Arbitration and Concilliation, 1914-1941 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Joint Board of Arbitration and Concilliation, 1914-1941 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Joint Board of Arbitration and Concilliation, 1914-1941 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- Joint Board of Arbitration and Concilliation, 1914-1941 (Box 23, Folder 11)
- Joint Board of Arbitration and Concilliation, 1914-1941 (Box 23, Folder 12)
- Joint Board of Arbitration and Concilliation, 1914-1941 (Box 23, Folder 13)
- Joint Board of Arbitration and Concilliation, 1914-1941 (Box 23, Folder 14)
- Joint Board of Arbitration and Concilliation, 1914-1941 (Box 23, Folder 15)
- Joint Board of Arbitration and Concilliation, 1914-1941 (Box 23, Folder 16)
- Joint Board of Arbitration and Concilliation, 1914-1941 (Box 23, Folder 17)